{
    "subject": "resource/HotRuby",
    "predicate": "ontology/programmingLanguage",
    "object": "resource/JavaScript",
    "human_readable": "HotRuby uses JavaScript as its programming language.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9587990641593933,
            "question": "Is JavaScript used in HotRuby?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9493297338485718,
            "question": "What programming language does HotRuby use?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8245319724082947,
            "question": "If you want to develop with HotRuby, what programming language should you know?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7929559350013733,
            "question": "What is the primary programming language for HotRuby development?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7675284147262573,
            "question": "Is Ruby the primary programming language used in HotRuby?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7607711553573608,
            "question": "What programming paradigm does HotRuby primarily use?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7461380958557129,
            "question": "What language powers the functionality of HotRuby?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5953577160835266,
            "question": "What is the core language underpinning HotRuby's structure?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5724774599075317,
            "question": "Which language is NOT used by HotRuby?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48070406913757324,
            "question": "Does HotRuby rely on Python for its syntax?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=HotRuby uses JavaScript as its programming language.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8299_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which language is NOT used by HotRuby?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8299_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the core language underpinning HotRuby's structure?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8299_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What language powers the functionality of HotRuby?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8299_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8299_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8299_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8299_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8299_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8299_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8299_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8299_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8299_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8299_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8299_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents state that \"HotRuby is also remarkable simply because it's written in JavaScript.\" and \"HotRuby is written in JavaScript which also works in Flash\".  This confirms that JavaScript is used in HotRuby."
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis response indicates that the information provided in the documents supports the statement that HotRuby uses JavaScript as its programming language. The documents mention that HotRuby is written in JavaScript and can run in a Flash environment, further supporting this claim."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}